Tired of searching for subtitles?
Ray generates them instantly: getray.app
In 197X. on a small island
on the outskirts of the Aleutians.
the second underground
nuclear detonation test took place.
As a result...
The nuclear test affected even
Monster Island. far to the south.
Godzilla vs. Megalon
Goro!
Looks like fun. huh? Want to ride it next?
I'd love that.
Care for a drink?
Sure.
Earthquake...
Rokuro! It's an earthquake! Come back!
I can't get back!
Get the life-rope gun!
Goro!
Goro! I can't do it!
Goro! W-What's that?
Hey! Here it comes!
Gotcha.
Let's go.
Similar cracks in the ground were
found along the North Pacific coast.
The seismological institute announced the
second underground nuclear detonation test
on Aska Island was the cause.
There could be further aftershocks.
This really is insane. We keep up these
nuclear tests and someday Earth will explode.
You're right.
If we find ourselves at the bottom
of the ocean like Lemuria or Mu.
it'll be the end of mankind.
What are Lemuria and Mu?
They're huge mythical continents
from three million years ago.
Lemuria in the Pacific Ocean
and Mu in the Atlantic.
But a diastrophism.
a major earthquake.
caused them to suddenly
sink into the oceans.
Maybe that earthquake
demolished your robot. huh?
Don't be such a pessimist. Catch.
Goro.
What?
The door's open. That's strange.
Damn it!
Crap...
Goro! Goro!
You all right?
I'm okay.
Rokuro!
You're both all right? Okay!
Damn it.
Hell. they really made a mess in here.
They didn't do anything
to my room. What about in here?
It's a total mess.
but they didn't take anything.
Really?
But I'll check again.
Okay.
Goro.
There's some funny powder here.
What do you think it is?
Looks like sand.
Son of a bitch...
Those were some funny burglars.
If they didn't take anything.
then what brought them here?
What's that?
A button from one of their suits.
It's the same color as that sand.
You're right.
What sand?
This.
Red sand. huh?
They must've dropped it.
We found it at the robot's feet.
Geology Lab
Hello.
Hi.
Oh? What are you making?
Baby rider.
Baby rider?
You're a racer. Can't you tell?
I'm still a rookie.
I had a rough time on the lake.
This one runs on the ground.
Will it run all right?
Leave it to me.
Are you sure?
You bet. It'll run.
I'm taking it for a test drive. Bye-bye.
Take care.
Hi.
Come in.
Okay.
Hello. Oh. it's finally complete.
It just needs finishing touches.
I've got results on the red sand and button.
What are they?
They come from
an undersea stratum 3.000 km deep.
Really?
Easter Island has similar sand.
Easter Island? Where's that?
It's a small uninhabited island
about 3.000 km east of Tahiti.
But huge statues of faces are
on this desolate island's slopes.
I hear the big ones
are about 20 meters tall.
They're about three million years old.
Now I'm more puzzled
than ever. Who was that man?
I'm done! Hey. it's complete!
Congratulations. You're done at last.
Hey. Jinkawa.
let's name this robot "Jet Jaguar."
Jet Jaguar? Not bad. That works for me.
That works for me.
Help!
The eyes are TV cameras.
It also has an automatic control device.
It can quickly evade obstacles.
Wow. well done.
Electrical engineers
do some amazing things.
Welcome home. It's unlocked.
That's...
Shit!
Seatopia... Seatopia...
This is Seatopia. Reception is good.
It's good here too.
We've just occupied the robotics lab
and captured the researchers.
Good. Well done.
Make the robot guide
Megalon to its attack targets.
My people...
Our undersea kingdom of Seatopia has
maintained peace for three million years.
But that peace was finally disturbed by the
reckless nuclear tests of the surface dwellers.
Our northern sector
was destroyed completely.
We've decided the only way to protect
Seatopia is to fight the surface dwellers.
We do this now for the peace of
the undersea kingdom of Seatopia!
For Seatopia!
Megalon.
Megalon!
Awaken. Megalon!
Go to the surface.
Crush the surface dwellers. the enemies
of our underwater kingdom. Seatopia.
Crush them!
Go. Megalon!
Goro!
Yeah.
Where's Mr. Jinkawa?
He's not here.
It's iron. We're in
some kind of iron box.
What'll we do?
I bet they're going to kill us!
Take it easy. Rokuro.
First off. think you can untie this rope?
Got it yet?
Almost there.
JSWContainer
Goro!
You all right?
Keep trying.
How far is Lake Kitayama?
About an hour or so. right?
Yeah.
I still don't get why you want to drop the
container into a crack at the bottom of the lake.
What's in it?
That's none of our business. But he'll
pay us •100.000 just to transport it.
Damn it...
Where are the others?
I got it untied.
Thank you. Rokuro.
The robot has arrived at
Lake Kitayama. It's standing by.
Understood.
And the robot creator
and his brother are in transit.
Understood.
The geothermal transport elevator is
ascending towards the Lake Kitayama fissure.
Where are you taking them?
Seatopia. the undersea kingdom.
Seatopia?
Yes.
Three million years ago. our ancestors
were fortunately inside a huge bubble when
the continent of Lemuria sank into the ocean.
They created oxygen and an artificial sun.
and built the kingdom of Seatopia.
So it's true...
Our science is therefore
far more advanced than yours.
If it is. why did you want the robot?
There aren't many of us.
We need many robots to protect ourselves
against enemies who threaten our peace.
I see. That's why you kidnapped them.
What kind of vehicle did you
take them in? Tell me! Tell me!
What kind of vehicle?
You'd better say it!
A container truck...
There. you're untied.
Ow!
Goro!
Ouch!
You okay?
Surface One. Surface One.
This is Surface One.
This is the robotics lab. A young man
who knows our secret escaped.
He's trying to catch up to the robot's
creator. Pursue him immediately!
Megalon has just arrived. I'm going
to have it attack Tokyo immediately.
Understood.
We have a special news report.
At 1:03 PM today. a new monster
appeared out of the Lake Kitayama fissure.
It's heading eastward. inflicting
considerable damage on local homes.
No way. Let's toss the container
at the dam and get outta there.
Well. mister? That's just as
good as putting it in the fissure.
No. Go there!
That's crazy!
Halt!
Disembark!
Get into position!
Goro. it stopped shaking.
Yeah...
Goro!
Watch out!
What was that sound?
It's the monster!
Give us a ride!
We've gotta go...
Where's the guy in brown?
We took care of him on the way here!
Put that container down first.
We don't have time!
Please! The container!
Shut up!
Damn it...
Rokuro!
You all right?
Goro. Goro!
You okay?
Jinkawa...
lsn't that Jet Jaguar flying overhead?
You're right! It's Jet Jaguar!
Damn it. He's under their control.
It'd be great if Jet Jaguar
could go call Godzilla.
All right. I'll try.
Try what?
I actually made him controllable via ultrasonic
waves in case computer control went out.
No good.
Why?
Ultrasonic waves only
work if we can see him.
Open fire!
You're saying
Jet Jaguar will bring Godzilla?
Yes.
But isn't he being
controlled by a computer?
Yes. but the computer control will
stop if ultrasonic waves are used.
So it'll work?
It will.
Jet Jaguar! Stop!
What happened to the robot?
Go to Monster Island.
Hurry and bring Godzilla.
We have a problem. The surface dwellers
have control of the robot again.
What's it doing?
It looks like it's going to ask Godzilla for help.
All right. Remain there.
Look for a chance
to regain control of the robot.
Understood.
Contact Space Hunter Nebula-M
and ask for Gigan's help.
Yes. sir.
Send the message via Easter Island.
It's started to behave erratically.
That's because it lost its pilot.
Over there!
Hello! Is anyone here?
Hello!
Maybe they all evacuated.
It looks like it.
I guess we'll have to borrow this.
Here we go.
Okay.
Damn it!
Take this. jerkface!
Rokuro!
Goro!
You beat him?
Yes.
Jet Jaguar went to get Godzilla too.
Really?
Yeah.
The monster's coming.
We've got to go.
What'll we do with him?
Let's carry him.
Quit struggling!
Never mind. Let's just go!
C'mon!
A message has come from
Space Hunter Nebula-M.
Space monster Gigan has departed.
Jet Jaguar! Jet Jaguar's back!
Really?
See? Look.
Yeah.
All right!
Jet Jaguar!
Ask him if he got in touch with Godzilla.
Okay.
Huh?
That's funny. He flew away even though
you didn't use an ultrasonic command.
Jet Jaguar! Come down!
Jet Jaguar! Come back!
This doesn't work anymore.
I guess something stimulated
Jet Jaguar's brain while he was running.
and it must've given him his own will.
His own will?
You mean he'll act on his own from
now on. without listening to human orders?
You see that and you're still going?
I know it's risky.
But I made Jet Jaguar with my own hands.
If anything bad happens to him...
I understand. You're his father.
I can't argue with that.
Look how huge Jet Jaguar is.
I can't believe it.
But he decided he had to fight
Megalon until Godzilla got here.
His determination made
him grow that big. I think.
Yay!
It's Gigan!
On whose side?
Megalon's. of course.
Oh!
Goro! It's Godzilla!
Godzilla!
Geothermal energy explosives unit.
prepare to seal all surface fissures.
Hurry!
Seal all fissures!
Bye-bye!
Godzilla! Bye-bye!
Goro.
Good job. Jet Jaguar!
Jet Jaguar! Thank you!
Jet Jaguar. come home with us.
Okay? Come home with us!
Okay?
Okay. Jet Jaguar?
Goro. use that thing.
Right.
Jet Jaguar.
want to come home with us?
What's happened to him?
Maybe his will is gone
now that his duty is done.
But maybe he'll find it again
if another fight like this happens.
We have to make sure one doesn't.
The undersea kingdom wouldn't have fought
if their peace hadn't been threatened.
Hey! Hey! Jet Jaguar!
Jet Jaguar!
A man-made guardian of Earth.
Jet Jaguar. Jet Jaguar.
Well done. Jaguar.
Go! Go! Defend our peace.
Display the courage that amazes us all.
Godzilla and Jaguar. punch. punch. punch!
Punch! Punch! Punch!
Let's all fight bravely as a team!
The End
DVDRip by cjdijk.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today